My name is Tina Turner.
That's.
I'm the owner of E2
Queen Brides and Beauty Salon.
Now, we were in 15 year Bridge of St,
and at the moment
I'm doing a medium brace
for my lovely client.
We came to Cornwall from
is where my husband
used to live in 2021.
We met in Ethiopia,
we used to live in Ethiopia
and then a war started in Ethiopia
and it was in a safe place
to raise our young children.
So we decided to move
where he used to live.
That's how we came straight to
Farm is from TV,
and I started doing here 2022.
But that's after
a lot of
encourage from my husband's house
because I wasn't sure
that there would be any clients.
But that was because
I haven't seen many of us
round after starting the hair.
I realize that people travel miles
to do the hair
and there wasn't a salon
dedicated for the afro.
Okay, looking you have.
So I said, It's a good opportunity for me
and also for the community
to have something dedicated just for them.
People come from all over Cornwall
and recently they even start
coming from Plymouth.
So hearing those stories
and seeing the excitement
on people's face was beautiful.
That makes me feel really proud in
what I'm doing and to be there
for people who need it like this is
just the
beginning, I would say,
because I started alone and then now
I'm working with like two barbers and
opticians.
And also there are a lot of people
who's asking
for a lesson or like to teach them.
We have a space
for any black owned businesses
to kind of interact with each other
where everyone comes and
believe their business cards or tell us
a little bit of about themselves.
So I'm trying to connect the community
with the people who have different skills.
So yeah, you can come here, connect
with people,
do your hair and know your community.
So that's, that's why I would like to do
and that's what I'm doing at the moment.